by H.
Nogizaka Original
DON! It has started!
Nogizaka Cochunsical Banana House!
And here's Nogizaka!
Yay!
Ready, Queen!
Ladies and gentlemen, let's get started on today's project!
Let's go!
We're going to have a speed queen for the Instantaneous Power Training Course!
Instantaneous power is always required in variety shows, such as questions and reactions from the MCs!
This time, in order to survive in the variety show world, we are going to hold a competition where you will be forced to train your blink of an eye.
What is it that Nogizaka lacks the most?
Instantaneous force.
So that's what it's come to.
Yes, instantaneous power.
That's why Nogizaka is going to change drastically from here.
So after this broadcast, we'll all be up to speed.
Yes, yes.
Today, I mean, more speed than usual.
Speed?
Yes, yes.
So, what's the first thing you're going to do, Mr. Kimura?
Let's go.
Quick talk.
What, like rain talk?
It's "Immediately Talk"!
When the topic of the talk is announced, we'll give an episodic talk by pushing the button quickly.
Four people try it, and the one who can talk quickly wins.
The last person to talk will be given a drink with the program's customary "x".
Well, the content is not that elaborate, but it's okay.
It's okay if it's too far from the topic.
If you don't understand what I'm saying, I'll give you an X.
Looks fine, Ume.
It's too late.
You just started talking, but I was already thinking about it.
I was already thinking. I don't know what to say.
You can't think, you have to feel.
Thinking is feeling.
Episodic talk, a game of speed
First of all, these four tried their hand at it.
You all understand the rules, don't you?
We're going to be aggressive.
Are you okay with the water? You seem calm.
Don't worry, I'm surprisingly fast.
Shokichi, we're all seniors here, but we have to go.
Yes, I'll go as fast as I can.
Let's go. Here's the subject of the talk.
Oh, here it comes. Nice. Honest.
Honesty.
Well... I'm a bit addicted to sweets these days.
Sweets?
Kuromi-san introduced the best snacks.
Snacks.
I've found the best snacks, too.
Great, I'd like to know.
Yes, it's called Kataage Potato.
You know, kataage potatos.
That's right.
That one.
You bought them online?
I bought a box.
There are 20 bags in a box.
One box of lightly salted.
Snack pepper flavor, one box.
Wow, that's great.
It arrived like a package from a vendor.
I still haven't eaten all of them.
The most recent thing I bought online was a box of kataage fries.
Oh, wow!
I bought 20 bags.
Wow, they're good.
They're good, aren't they?
I don't know why we're talking about this.
It's just something you buy on the Internet these days.
It's good!
It's good.
It's a bit of a screw-up story.
There's also a link to last week.Some links to last week.
Hey.
It's pretty good.
Okay.
Yay!
Fifth-year student Sugawara is out, leaving us with three.
Here's the next subject.
Let's talk about what happened backstage. Tsutsuki's already pushed it.
You're early, Tsutsui. I'm sure there's a backstage story.
Okay, Tsutsui, please.
The make-up artist gave me some taro kenpies.
I love taro kenpies, so I wanted to try one.
I asked him if I could have one and he put it in a paper cup.
But when I came to, they were all gone.
I ate them all! I ate them all!
Hiro-san, are you okay with this? Isn't this wonderful?
I ate it all! It's just like an idol!
Hiro, you're not too picky. I don't know what part of you is not picky.
I don't know what's missing... when I go to live shows, I don't laugh at all during the MC.
Only Hiro-san laughs. He laughs at stories that aren't funny at all.
Either one of them is hurting you or both of them are hurting you.
There's only two people left... who can avoid parts...
Kubo and Ayaka... are you pushing?
They're pushing... and losing.
It was a really good story.
I wanted to talk.
They wanted to talk.
That's show business.
It's true, isn't it?
If you don't go to the speaking part, you can't speak.
Kubo and Ayaka are duking it out.
A change of subject. This way.
This way.
You're early.
It's family bragging.
Family bragging.
The previous captain, Manatsu Akimoto...
Akimoto Manatsu, the previous captain, was talking on the radio about what kind of life she wanted to lead if she hadn't joined Nogizaka.
"If I hadn't joined Nogizaka, what kind of life would I have wanted?
She said, "If I had gone to college like a normal student...
If I had gone to a normal college, I would have entered a beauty contest and won it.
I would have won the contest, become a female announcer and get married.
I didn't tell her at that time.
I didn't tell her at the time.
My sister actually won the Miss Contest at her university.
Wow!
That's a great story.
She's the king of harmony!
Seriously, the king of Kazumi.
The introduction is a bit... It's because of Kiyoto's story, isn't it?
Perfect.
So, Hayakawa...
Too bad, Hayakawa.
He lost.
No, I'll use Hayakawa's name.
Hayakawa always says yes.
But with buttons, it's not good at all.
I wanted to show off my family.
I can't do it.
No, no, no, no.
Here's your punishment.
The remaining losers, the Hayakawa's, will get a spring version of the punishing drink.
Did you want to brag about your family?
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please drink it.
Here you go.
It's really good for your throat.
I've been pushing it from the beginning.
I've been pushing it.
I wanted to make my family proud.
I don't know why.
I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry.
I was more proud of you than I was of her.
More than her.
I don't understand.
Next, Mr. Hinohara, please.
Imitate him right away!
Here we go.(expression of) effort or strain
What the hell?
The four players challenged each other in this showdown as well.
First, when you see a genre of mimicry, you have to push the button to win the right to answer.
Then, as soon as they see the name of the subject, they are asked to perform the imitation.
Sounds interesting!
It's pretty much the same thing as in TV shows, when you do an impersonation and suddenly you're doing it in a jerk-off way.
It's this spontaneity that makes people laugh.
It's this sense of speed, isn't it?
After a while, they'll be like, "Oh yeah!
Because it's that speed.
It's okay to do it that way.
That's why it's funny.
Yeah, let's go for it.
What? Are you in?
No, no, no. I just said I'll do my best.
Mr. Hinohara, you're in?
No, no, I mean good luck.
I mean, good luck.
Can I do it?
Just here. Mr. Hinohara will join us.
No, no, no, I'm in!
So, the four of us, with the strongest qualifications, try our hand at a quick-push mimicry.
We're not so good at mimicking... although I often mimic other members.
Well, yes.
Mr. Hinohara is in this group, so if you lose by pushing, you're out of luck.
seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously...
Let's go!
Please push this button for the mimicry genre.
It's too early!
Too soon!
Sorry, I told you to press the button.
Please push when you see the genre.
Wow, you're so aggressive.
You're so aggressive, Yumiki.
There's crazy in there.
The first one to get motivated in a battle royale.
Scary, scary.
I've got to do it. I've got to do it.
I'm scared.
I'm in.
Okay, I'm ready.
Immediately, we have a male comedian.
A male comedian. Who will he be?
Who will you have him do?
You'd better get a louder reaction.
I'll watch.
It's so good!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The louder the reaction, the better.
It's good! It's good!
It's good!
But it's funny because it's done at this speed.
It's just groaning.
That's right.
You did it!
We did it.
We've got to crush them more.
Oh, man.
That was so great.
I haven't seen it yet.
I was really pushed over the edge.
Oh my God, that was so funny!
It's so funny!
Umemon!
Who will follow the captain's shocking impersonation?
Well, there are still three of us left.
Let's go! Here's the genre!
Yuna, you're losing.
She's losing.
He's losing.
Futoshi Chiba, this is the one for you.
Three, two, one, go ahead
Let's see, this table...
It's 1,000 yen.
It's a little high.
It's a little high, so it's easy to eat.It's so easy to eat at the table.
Where's Anmika's element?
It's not Kansai dialect.
This table...
It's Shibata.
It's perfect.
Just right... for eating rice.
Just right for eating rice.
Okay.
No, no, no, it's not Shibata at all, Nakano.
It's just Shibata introducing this table.
That's right.
What's with the Kansai dialect?
First of all, it's Kansai dialect.
Sorry.
The final showdown with Himura.
Oh no! It's a one-on-one battle between Yumeki and Himura.
It's not catching up.
He's losing.
Here we go. Genre...
You're wrong.
Yumeki, I wanted to do this.
I've always wanted to do animals.
Here's the animal for you, Yumeki.
Gorilla, three, two, one, go!
Why are you doing that?
Nice. But if Mr. Himura wins more gorillas, then Mr. Himura wins.
Very serious. Very serious.
Don't lose, Yumeki.
Yumeki's OK.
We did it! We did it!
We did it!
You really went all out, didn't you, Yumeki?
Yes. I thought it's important to be quick-witted and swinging with all your might.
That's right.
I did.
That's nice.
No, it was really ugly.
You shook it off well.
You did it.
You guys did great.
That's great.
You know, impersonations can be funny even when they don't look like you.
That's true.
They're all funny.
That's for sure.
So, Mr. Nimura, here's your punishment.
I lost.
That sucks.
Please drink.
Stinky! Stinky!
Stinky!
No, stinky!
Ugh!
I have to drink this stuff just because I lost at the push of a button!
After this, the opening of Haranmoto?
From here on, it's a battle for Soto-kun!
This time, Yori here is the entrant!
Kawasaki, this is one of your seniors.
Yes, sir!
Don't be afraid, you have to go fast!
I don't want to be punished, so I'll do my best!
No, it's true.
You have this kind of feeling, don't you, Kawasaki?
You've done this before, right?
You know, when you're suddenly asked to do something.
I'm not a fast pusher yet.
But you're pushing the button in your mind.
Yes, you have to do it with that feeling.
Yes, that's right.
And Kawaki?
Yes.
Kawaki, you always act so strange.
That's right.
I get mad at him when he goes through something.
That's probably why.
Hey, you're still acting weird.
I think I can work on this.
Great.That's good.
Sato, too. We have to go for it.
You've got to go for it.
It's your moment.
That's right.
Go for it.
I'll do my best to get first place.
Okay, here we go.
Immediately, your subject, here!
Here it is! You're early!
Yes, sir!
Okay, Tou-kun, please!
Yes, I love makeup,
Well, I put my eyelashes up more firmly than usual today!
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha!
So this is what you mean.
I want a little more, don't you?
A little bit then.
I'd like to see a little more. A little bit.
Okay, one more time with the makeup!
Does this mean I have to laugh?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
If you get a laugh, it's better.
Be aggressive!
Yes, Takagi!
Yes, sir!
Yes, makeup, please!
I'm not interested in makeup at all.
I never really touched makeup until I joined Nogizaka.
Oh, you haven't?
That's right. That's why I haven't gone to department stores to buy cosmetics.
That's why I've never been to a department store to buy cosmetics.
What?
After four years...
You've never gone shopping?
I've never gone shopping.
Yeah, well...
Well, someone did.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, OK!
That was OK?
Because it was funny.
Oh, because it was funny?
So that was talk. That was talk.
Can someone please go?
Kaki is very far away and out of position. Three left.
We've got to keep going.
Come on!
Here we go, and here's the next subject!
That's it, right? Weird long and thin thing.
Last night's dinner was dangmyun.
Do you know what tammyun is?
It's all the rage among young people these days.
I know!
How about this? Lucky.
Lucky, of course.
But it's no good. It's no good. Not like this.
Great. Then no.
Last night's dinner was me.
I'll go again with last night's dinner. Yo, start!
Nothing at last night's dinner!
Oh, here it comes! I did it!
Guess what I had for dinner last night?
Huh? Dangmyun.
You guessed it!
It was dinner, Dangmyun!
Last night's dinner was chicken bentou.
What's chicken bentou?
Actually, it was served in Atami.
I had chicken bentou in Atami.
Well, that's all right.
The point is, we just need to know who he is.
I covered it.
But it's okay.
Who will be punished, Sato or Kawasaki?
Kawasaki's not aggressive at all.
Yes, but I'll definitely push next time.
Let's push! Let's push!Let's push. Let's push.
Two strong guys, Sato and Kawasaki.
Okay, here we go. Here's the subject.
Oh, wow!
I think I pushed it before I saw it.
Kawasaki, go ahead.
I usually have a bad memory.
But I can remember the faces of the people who come to see the chestnuts.
I'm really good at talking... face-to-face.
I'm really good at that.
If you come again, I'm sure I'll say...
I'll say, "Long time no see.
Are you sure you can say that?
I'm getting a little nervous.
That was cute.
It's all right.
This is difficult.
It's like this.
I'm the first one to press the button, and then it resumes.
That's right, that's why it's a little bit...
I thought it was just about the eyelashes.
That's what happened.
I'd like to learn how to speak.
Is there anywhere good?
Here, here.
This is where I talk.
And watch TV.
Watch TV and watch people who want to speak like them.
That's the textbook.
Watch TV.
And practice haionji.
You don't need to teach haionji.
Rika Sato of the Haiku Onshi Department will be punished with a drink.
Please.
It's so bad! You're not allowed to drink water afterwards.
Oh, that's terrible!
Now we'll have the second round of mimicry, and we'll have Shimoda again.
I don't think Endo or Inoue have this kind of explosive power.
But if we lose, we have to drink. Yota's probably going to go.
I don't know anything about him.
I'm afraid of the pattern of not knowing what you're talking about
But there's gorillas and gorillas I know gorillas
You know the gorilla, too. I know what he looks like.
If you ask me to do a moniker, I don't know what's a quote
But you know gorillas. I know gorillas.
What's the matter with you? You're the only one who understands gorillas.
Endo, are you okay? I don't think he's going to do anything like that.
Or mimicry. No, I won't do it.
I've never done an impersonation before.
Then again, you saw how he did it this time.
Remember... how Umeme came out?
You'd better react louder.
You've got to be louder.
I can't stand to watch that.
Look, that was fun.
Shibata's shamisen was fun.
This desk is great.
Perfect for eating.
Who's that?
How about Inoue?
I don't do impersonations, and I don't watch much TV.
I don't watch much TV, so when a celebrity or comedian comes on...
You know the gorilla, don't you? I know the gorilla.
Oh, come on, gorillas are so famous.
I'll never take Yodato-inoue again when the animals come out.
After this, new characters will be active one after another.
I'm going to push the button as soon as the genre is chosen.
I'm going to go to the imitation genre.
The end!
I'm not going to get it!
Yag!
It's called "Yag.
You're going to do a yag.
What's a yag?
It's a yag.
Here you go.
I don't know.
Tsuda, right?
Tsuda, right.
Ryan Tsuda.I'm going to Ryan Tsuda.
What's that?
Tsuda.
321, please.
Goi goi goi.
A little more, please.
Goigoisu.
It's more of a shape... choreography, choreography.
There's some kind of choreography.
There's a choreography.
Goigois
Okay, okay.
Good job, good job!
"Goigoisu" is so cute.
It's cute.
You did a good job, didn't you?
Did you work hard?
I did my best, and I pushed pretty fast.
Very fast!
I got there faster than I expected.
You're losing, Mr. Himura.
I'm pushing.
I'm...
Endo's gone.
I'm glad.
I knew you had the courage to do it.
You're right.
Courage.
Straight ahead, Endo's in first place, followed by Courage.
Let's go... this way.
This one's good.
I don't know... maybe I don't know... what should I do?
I don't know... maybe it's okay...
I'm going to ask you to do this impersonation.
I haven't seen it.
Okay, here we go.
Cameraman.
I'd like to see him do a speaking imitation.
I'd like to see him talk.
What?
He's doing his impersonation of Monkey King.
I'm the Monkey King.
Okay, okay, a little more.
I'm Monkey King!
Give me something more, give me something more, talk.
I'm going to beat you.
I'm not going to say that.
You might say it, but you'll fight.
I've never heard him say he's going to beat you.
I'll beat you.
Okay.
You really don't know, do you?
He did a good job... saying "Ola Goku.
He said "Mamehame" too.
But it's just an atmosphere.
You're really losing it, Mr. Himura.
I've been pushing him all day.
Did you do it, Goku?
Of course I can do it.
Try it.
My stomach hurts! Hey! Don't shake! Hey! To the planks!
All right, all right, all right, all right.
If you can push it.
I can't even push "goigoi"!
Goigoi goi goi goi!
Okay, okay, okay.
I wish I could push it.
But you all have a pattern of saying it loud and strong.
Yes, that's true.
Mr. Himura is a pro at this.
He'll do it right away.
It's a game.
Don't worry.
Inoue, all you have to do is win the absolute button.
Yes, sir.
Okis Inoue, can you beat Pro Himura?
Okay, let's go to the end.
Imitation genre here!
Ok!
Himura-sanMr. Hizumura.
I want to do this.
I don't know yet.
Even if I don't know yet, I might get punished.
Good luck, Inoue!
Here are the animals you'll be working with.
Chicken.
Let's go!
Three, two, one.
What's that?
KOKKEKO!
Do more.
Chicken?
Come on in, chicken.
You'll get a "X".
Kokketsukko, shout more!
It's morning. Yell more.
Kids...
Yes, it's OK.
Wow!
I was actually going to put "X" on it, but I tried my best.
That's good enough.
The first kokkogio was really interesting.
It was a very interesting first game.
What's this aside? You've been wanting to do something?
I can do animals.
Oh, really? You can do chickens?
Yes, I can.
Come on, give me a hand.
Well, well, well.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, he's just gonna puke.
That's good. That's funny. That's hilarious.
How did that come out of the earthquake?
Mr. Himura, your punishment game.
Drink up, please. It stinks!
Chicken! Chicken!
That's a yoga chicken!
Asuka Saito's graduation concert is on sale.
I'm Ryoma Hayashi.
You've noticed, right? You do, right? No, right? No, it's not. What's that? I'm doing a beautiful woman in 2020 or so.
I cut my bangs to make me look younger. Did you notice?
Please subscribe to our channel!